Guide to the Arthur Jack Viseltear papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Professional Activities, 1963-1989; Series II
  - National Institutes of Health
    - Proposal to study British public health in the eighteenth century, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 72)
    - Study Section, 1973-1987 (Box 19, Folder 73-75)
  - Oxford University Press, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 76)
  - Robert Wood Johnson Health Policy Fellowship Program
    - General, 1973-1988 (Box 19, Folder 77-79)
    - Board report, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 80-81)
    - Carter, Tim Lee
      - General, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 82-83)
      - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 84-85)
        See also: Series I, folder 35
      - Drafts of "National Health Education and Disease Prevention Act", 1975 (Box 20, Folder 86)
    - Kennedy, Edward M. (Box 20)
      - General, 1975 April-December (Box 20, Folder 87-95)
      - General, 1976-1986 (Box 21, Folder 96)
      - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 97-98)
      - Senate bill 1466, Disease Control Amendments Act, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 99)
      - Senate bill 1467, National Health Education and Promotion Act, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 100)
      - Senate bill 1521, National Health Education Policy and Development Act, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 101-102)
      - Senate bill 1737, Clinical Laboratories Improvement Act
        - General, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 103-104)
        - Background material, 1963-1975 (Box 21, Folder 105-106)
        - Correspondence, 1975 January-September (Box 22, Folder 107-114)
        - Correspondence, 1975 October-1976 (Box 23, Folder 115-120)
        - Hearings, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 121-122)
        - Questions for witnesses, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 123)
        - Testimony, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 124-125)
        - Witnesses [requests to testify, curricula vitae], 1975 (Box 24, Folder 126-127)
    - Promotion of program, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 128-129)
  - United States
    - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare
      - Health Services and Mental Health Administration [proposal], 1969 (Box 24, Folder 130)
      - National Center for Health Services [proposal], 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 131-132)
    - Senate. Health subcommittee, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 133-136)
  - University of California. School of Public Health. [grant for research], 1968 (Box 24, Folder 137)
  - University of North Carolina Press, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 138)
  - Yale Journal of Biology and Medicine, 1975-1988 (Box 24, Folder 139)
  - Yale New Haven Hospital Archives Committee, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 140)
  - Yale University
    - General, 1971-1989 (Box 25, Folder 141)
    - Health Policy and Management Interest Group, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 142)
    - History Department, 1981-1989 (Box 25, Folder 143)
    - Library
      - Contemporary Medical Care and Health Policy Collection
        - General, 1973-1989 (Box 25, Folder 144-152)
        - Grant proposal, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 153)
      - Medical history collection [proposal], 1984 (Box 26, Folder 154)
      - Sigerist papers, 1979-1987 (Box 26, Folder 155)
    - Saybrook College, 1975-1988 (Box 26, Folder 156)
    - School of Medicine
      - General, 1971-1989 (Box 26, Folder 157)
      - Academic Progress Committee, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 158)
      - Advisory Committee on Medical Ethics, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 159)
      - Basic Sciences Curriculum Committee, 1986-1989 (Box 26, Folder 160-165)
      - Committee on Exhibitions in the Cushing Rotunda, 1986-1989 (Box 26, Folder 166)
      - Committee on Future Tenure Policy, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 167)
      - Committee on Planning and Priorities, 1976-1978 (Box 26, Folder 168)
      - Community Medicine Track [planning committee], 1970-1973 (Box 26, Folder 169)
      - Curriculum Committee, 1980-1983 (Box 26, Folder 170)
      - Epidemiology and Public Health
        - General, 1971-1988 (Box 26, Folder 171)
        - General, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 172)
        - Center for Health Policy and Resources, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 173)
        - Division of Health Policy and Resources, 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 174)
        - Five year mission plan, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 175)
        - School of Organization and Management and Epidemiology and Public Health [proposal to Pew Memorial Trust], 1982 (Box 27, Folder 176)
      - Health Manpower Challenge for the Eighties [conference], 1981 (Box 27, Folder 177)
      - Health Services Administration
        - Ad Hoc Committee to Review M.P.H. Essay, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 178)
        - Impact of Federal Legislation on Connecticut, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 179)
        - Proposal for a program in medical care, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 180)
        - Proposal for a Research and Teaching Program in History and Policy of Health Services, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 181-183)
      - History of Medicine
        - General (Box 27)
          - 1977-1985 (Box 27, Folder 184-186)
          - 1986-1989 (Box 28, Folder 187-190)
        - Sigerist Lectures, 1978-1984 (Box 28, Folder 191)
      - Humanities in Medicine Advisory Board, 1984-1989 (Box 28, Folder 192)
      - Marguerite Lerner Award Committee, 1985-1989 (Box 28, Folder 193)
      - Medical Library Committee, 1981-1989 (Box 28, Folder 194)
      - Medical School Council, 1978-1986 (Box 28, Folder 195)
      - Self-Study Task Force, 1982-1983 (Box 28, Folder 196)
      - Strategic Planning Task Force, 1985-1986 (Box 28, Folder 197)
      - Study group on tenure, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 198)
      - Task Force for Developing a Course for Medical Students on Professional Responsibility, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 199)
      - Task Force on the Medical Curriculum, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 200)
      - Transfusion Medicine Academic Award, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 201)
      - Weinerman Memorial Fund Committee, 1969-1989 (Box 29, Folder 202-214)
    - Women of Yale Project, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 215)
- Writings, Speeches and other Statements, 1959 1989, undated; Series III
  The files in this series are divided into three sections: published writings, unpublished writings, and public statements. Files in each section may contain drafts, notes, outlines, and any associated correspondence. The series does not include notes for course lectures, which are in Series IV.
  The published writings section is composed of journal articles followed by book reviews. Each type of published writing is arranged in chronological order. A bibliography of these publications is attached to Viseltear's résumé in the biographical folder in Series VI.
  Viseltear's unpublished writings include book projects, journal articles, and his doctoral dissertation. Some of these files are for large projects left incomplete at the time of Viseltear's death and are of overlapping and/or indeterminate date. The files in this section are arranged, therefore, only in rough chronological order. For some book projects, there are files of research notes, which are arranged by Viseltear's topical categories. The subjects of the unpublished writings are similar to those of the published writings, and it is possible that some of the unpublished drafts were used as the basis for a later published title
  The massive research files for the C. E. A. Winslow biography contain notes on Winslow's colleagues, professional associations, parents, and schools. There are more than 3,000 photocopies, mainly of professional correspondence, from the Winslow Papers in the Yale Library, but there are only a few drafts of chapters.
  The "333 Cedar Street" files contain research materials and successive drafts for a history of the Yale Medical School. These include interviews with students, faculty, and staff, which provide personal insights into contemporary medical education issues. The interviewees discuss premedical education, the medical school, its curriculum, the Yale System, colleagues, specialty choices, clinical and laboratory experiences, issues for women and minorities, and their future plans. Both tapes and transcripts are available for most of the nearly fifty interviews, arranged alphabetically by the initial of the last name. The full names are given when they are known. The transcriptions include handwritten drafts and/or typed versions. The original tapes may not be played. For information on copies created for research use consult the Audio Tape appendix.
  The public statements include lectures, introductory remarks, and radio talks. The lecture files are arranged chronologically and document invited talks at academic institutions and papers contributed at professional meetings. Talks given at a colleague's course or contributed to a seminar program are in the folder "Guest lectures." Radio talks, at the end of the series, include Viseltear's contributions to two programs on public health. On "Doctors in Society," a public affairs program on the role of the physician in society and the quality of health care in California, Viseltear discusses contemporary health issues that echo eighteenth century concerns.
  - Published
    - Journal articles
      - "The Last Illness of Sir Robert Walpole"
        - Drafts, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 1)
        - Notes, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - "Doctors of Medicine and Doctors of Osteopathy in California", 1967-1969 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - "Joanna Stephens and the Eighteenth Century Lithontropics", 1968 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - "Historical Development of Public Health", 1968 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - "Compulsory Health Insurance in California, 1915-1918", 1969 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - "The California Medical-Economic Survey", 1970 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - "Compulsory Health Insurance in California, 1934-1942", 1971 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - "Emergence of the Medical Care Section of APHA, 1926-1948", 1972 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - "The Pneumonic Plague Epidemic of 1924 in Los Angeles", 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 10)
        - Notes, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 11-14)
      - "Health Education and Public Policy: A Short History of P.L. 94-317", 1976 (Box 30, Folder 15)
      - "Immunization and Public Policy: A Short Political History of the Swine Flu Legislation", 1977 (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - "George Rosen (June 3, 1910-July 27, 1977)" (Box 31, Folder 17)
      - "Cancer Control in the Context of Post World War II Health Policy", 1978 (Box 31, Folder 18)
      - "Charles-Edward Amory Winslow", 1980 (Box 31, Folder 19)
      - "Looking Back at Tomorrow"
        - General, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 20)
        - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 21)
      - "C.-E. A. Winslow and the Definition of Public Health", 1982 (Box 31, Folder 22)
      - "C.-E. A. Winslow and the Early years of Public Health at Yale, 1915-1925", 1982 (Box 31, Folder 23)
      - "John R. Paul and the Definition of Preventive Medicine", 1982 (Box 31, Folder 24)
      - "The Last Illnesses of Sir Robert and Horace Walpole"
        - Correspondence and notes, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 25)
        - Drafts, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 26)
      - "Milton C. Winternitz and the Yale Institute of Human Relations"
        - Correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 31, Folder 27)
        - Drafts, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 28)
      - "333 Cedar Street, an Oral History", 1984-1985 (Box 31, Folder 29)
      - "Oral History and Contemporary Medical Edcation", 1986 (Box 31, Folder 30)
      - "The Yale Plan of Medical Education"
        - Abstract, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 31)
        - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 32)
        - Drafts, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 33)
        - Notes, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 34)
      - "Carpooling for Friendship and Sanity", 1986 (Box 32, Folder 35)
      - "C.E. A. Winslow and the Later Years of Public Health at Yale, 1940-1945", 1987 (Box 32, Folder 36-38)
    - "The Evolution of Pioneering Health Education Programs in the United States", 1988 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Book reviews (Box 32)
      - General, 1965-1987 (Box 32, Folder 40)
      - Boswell's Clap and Other Essays, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - Unpublished
    - Tulane University [student papers], 1959 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - University of California at Los Angeles [student papers], 1960-1963 (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - "Reader in the History of Public Health and Social Welfare" [correspondence, outlines], 1964 (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - "Renal and Vesicular Calculi in the Eighteenth Century" [draft, notes, outlines], 1965 (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - "A Brief Account of the Eighteenth Century Lithontropics" [drafts, notes], [1965] (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - "The Lithontropic Medicines of the Eighteenth Century" [Ph.D. dissertation])
      - Correspondence, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 47)
      - Manuscript, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 48-50)
      - Notes, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 51)
    - "Osteopathy: A Profession in Search of a Future" [book]
      - Bibliography, [1966] (Box 33, Folder 52)
      - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 33, Folder 53)
      - Interviews, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 54)
      - Note cards, [1966] (Box 34, Folder 55)
      - Notes, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 56-59)
      - Outlines, 1966-1967 (Box 34, Folder 60)
    - "The Case Method in Epidemiology" [draft, outline], 1967 (Box 34, Folder 61)
    - "Health Insurance in California, 1915-1918" [book]
      - Chapter I [outlines], 1968 (Box 34, Folder 62)
      - Chapter II, III, IV [drafts], 1968 (Box 34, Folder 63-64)
      - Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 34, Folder 65)
      - Notes (Box 34)
        - General, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 66-68)
        - Workmen's Compensation, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 69)
    - "A History of Personal and Public Hygiene" [drafts, outlines], [ca. 1965] (Box 35, Folder 70)
    - "A History of the Development of the Epidemiologic Methodology in the Eighteenth vs. the Nineteenth Centuries", [ca. 1966] (Box 35, Folder 71)
    - "Osteopathy in California" [outlines, notes for Chapter 1 of a book to be written with Arnold I. Kisch], [ca. 1966] (Box 35, Folder 72)
    - "Compulsory Health Insurance in California" [book concerning 1930s-1950s]
      - Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 35, Folder 73)
      - Grant proposals, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 74)
      - Notes, [1965-1971]
        - General (Box 35, Folder 75)
        - Bibliography (Box 35, Folder 76)
        - Biographies (Box 35, Folder 77)
        - California legislature (Box 35, Folder 78-79)
        - California Medical Association (Box 35, Folder 80)
        - California Physicians Service (Box 35, Folder 81)
        - California State Federation of Labor (Box 35, Folder 82)
        - Chapters IV and V (Box 35, Folder 83)
        - Commonwealth Club (Box 35, Folder 84-85)
        - Dodd Report (Box 36, Folder 86-87)
        - Health centers (Box 36, Folder 88)
        - Health surveys (Box 36, Folder 89)
        - Local medical society journals (Box 36, Folder 90)
        - Medical care journals (Box 36, Folder 91)
        - Nursing profession (Box 36, Folder 92)
        - Olson, Cuthbert L. (Box 36, Folder 93)
        - Periodical articles (Box 36, Folder 94-96)
        - State medicine (Box 36, Folder 97)
        - Warren, Earl (Box 36, Folder 98)
        - Watts Hospital (Box 36, Folder 99)
        - Western Hospital Association (Box 36, Folder 100)
      - Topical outlines, [197-] (Box 36, Folder 101)
    - "Historical Studies of Contemporary Health Insurance"
      - Grant application, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 102)
      - Notes on contemporary health insurance in New York, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 103)
    - "The Role of the Medical School in the Health Care System" [draft of chapter 1], 1976 (Box 37, Folder 104)
    - "Medical Care Teaching Program in the Department of Public Health, Yale University"
      - Drafts, [197-] (Box 37, Folder 105)
      - Notes, [197-] (Box 37, Folder 106-109)
    - "Medical Manpower and Public Policy: A Short History of P.L. 94-484", [197-] (Box 37, Folder 110)
    - "Social Forces Leading to the Establishment of Pioneering Public Health Education Programs in the United States"
      - Drafts, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 111-114)
      - Drafts, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 115)
      - Proposal for inclusion in "A History of Public Health: Britain and the United States Contrasted", 1987 (Box 38, Folder 116)
    - "Memorandum on the Value of the History of Medicine", 1987 (Box 38, Folder 117)
    - "Charles-Edward Amory Winslow: A Biography"
      - Correspondence, 1984-1988 (Box 38, Folder 118)
      - Drafts
        - Preface, [198-] (Box 38, Folder 119)
        - Chapter 2, M.I.T. [notes], [198-] (Box 38, Folder 120)
        - English School, [198-] (Box 38, Folder 121-122)
      - Grants, 1981-1987 (Box 38, Folder 123-124)
      - Notes, [198-] (Box 38)
        - General (Box 38, Folder 125-126)
        - American Journal of Public Health (Box 38, Folder 127)
        - American Public Health Association
          - Committee on Administrative Practice (Box 38, Folder 128)
          - Committee on History of Public Health (Box 39, Folder 129)
          - Committee on Hygiene of Housing (Box 39, Folder 130)
        - Association of Schools of Public Health (Box 39, Folder 131)
        - Conclusion (Box 39, Folder 132)
        - Emerson, Haven (Box 39, Folder 133)
        - Epidemiology (Box 39, Folder 134)
        - Falk, Isidore S. (Box 39, Folder 135)
        - Hospitals in 1930s (Box 39, Folder 136)
        - Journal of Bacteriology (Box 39, Folder 137)
        - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Box 39, Folder 138)
        - New York City (Box 39, Folder 139)
        - Parents (Box 39, Folder 140)
        - Public Health Bulletins (Box 39, Folder 141)
        - Schools of Public Health (Box 39, Folder 142)
        - Sedgewick, William T. (Box 39, Folder 143)
        - Walker, Francis (Box 39, Folder 144)
        - World War II (Box 39, Folder 145)
        - Yale University, 1940-1945 (Box 39, Folder 146)
        - Yale University. Department of Public Health (Box 39, Folder 147)
      - Outlines, 1984-1986 (Box 39, Folder 148)
      - Research files [notes and photocopies]
        - Files 1-2, items 1-229, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 149-150)
        - Files 3-9, items 230-963, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 151-157)
        - Files 10-14, items 965-1792, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 158-162)
        - Files 15-20, items 1793-2263, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 163-168)
        - Files 21-25, items 2264-3080, unnumbered, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 169-173)
        - Subject headings, 1984-1985 (Box 43, Folder 174)
        - Subject lists, topical outlines, [198-] (Box 43, Folder 175)
    - "333 Cedar Street" (Box 43)
      - Correspondence (Box 43)
        - General, 1981-1985 (Box 44, Folder 176)
        - Macy Foundation grant, 1980-1983 (Box 44, Folder 177)
      - Drafts (Box 44)
        - 1981 (Box 44, Folder 178-185)
        - 1982 (Box 45, Folder 186-187)
        - [1982] fragments (Box 45, Folder 188)
        - 1982 Oct 12 plus pages from 1983 Jan 5 (Box 45, Folder 189)
        - 1983-1984 (Box 45, Folder 190)
        - Drafts, outlines, notes, [198-] (Box 45, Folder 191)
        - Draft in three parts intended for Yale Journal publication, [198-] (Box 45, Folder 192)
      - Interviews (Box 45)
        - Original tapes
          Conditions Governing Access
          Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
          - A., G. K. professor, Psychiatry and Pharmacology [tape 1], 1981 (Box 46)
          - A., J. E. 4th year M.D. student [tapes 2, 3, 4 (side 1)], 1981 (Box 46)
          - Adimora, Adoa, 4th year M.D. student [tapes 5, 6 (side 1)], 1981 (Box 46)
          - B., H. R. associate professor, Medicine [tape 7], 1981 (Box 46)
          - B., S. M. 4th year M.D. student [tape 12] (Box 46)
          - Baserga, Susan, 3d year M.D./Ph.D. student [tape 11], 1982 (Box 46)
          - Boulpaep, Emile, professor and chairman, Physiology [tapes 13, 14, 15, 16 (side 1)], 1984 (Box 46)
          - Brizendine, Louann 5th year M.D. student [tape 8], 1981 (Box 46)
          - C., J. R. 3d year M.D. student, Primary Care [tape 19], 1981 (Box 46)
          - Chaillet, J. Richard, 5th year M.D./Ph.D student [tapes 20, 21, 22], 1981 (Box 46)
          - Codish, Kay D. Director of the Office of Women in Medicine [tapes 17, 18 (side 1)], 1981 (Box 46)
          - Duncomb, David C. chaplain, Medical School [tape 23], 1981 (Box 46)
          - Duffy, Thomas P. professor, Medicine [tape 24], 1982 (Box 46)
          - F,. E. R. H. 3d year M.D./M.P.H. student [tapes 25, 26, 27 (side 1)]; Viseltear's narrative about the interview [tape 27 (side 2)], 1981 (Box 46)
          - Fryer, Regina Kenny, medical reference librarian [tape 28], 1981 (Box 46)
          - Guido, Annette D. 4th year M.D. student [tapes 29, 30], 1981 (Box 46)
          - Garber, J. E. 5th year M.D./Ph.D. student [tapes 31, 32], 1981 (Box 46)
          - Garcia-Blanco, Marcia, 4th year M.D./Ph.D. student [tapes 9, 10], 1981 (Box 46)
          - Goldman, Robert S. 4th year M.D. student [tapes 33, 34, 35], 1981 (Box 46)
          - H., B. medical school alumnus, 1981 [tape 36], 1982 (Box 46)
          - Homer, Robert J. 2d year M.D./Ph.D. student [tapes 6 (one side), 38, 39], 1981 (Box 46)
          - Horwitz, Ralph I. assistant professor, Medicine [tape 37, Viseltear's narrative about the interview on tape 53 (side 2)], 1981 (Box 46)
          - J., R. E. 3d year M.D. student [tapes 40, 41], 1981 (Box 46)
          - Kinder, Barbara, assistant professor, Surgery [tape 42], 1982 (Box 46)
          - L., R. M.D./Ph.D. candidate [tape 43], 1981 (Box 46)
          - L., R. associate professor, Medicine [tape 44, 45], 1982, 1983 (Box 46)
          - Levine, Robert J. professor, Medicine [tapes 46, 47], 1981 (Box 46)
          - M., J. T. secretary, Internal Medicine [tape 48], 1981 (Box 46)
          - M., S. K. medical reference librarian [tape 49, 50 (side 1)], 1981 (Box 46)
          - Matory, Yvedt L. 4th year M.D. student [tape 51, 52, 53 (side 1)], 1981 (Box 47)
          - Nestler, Eric J. M.D./Ph.D. student [tape 54], 1981 (Box 47)
          - P., H. A. 3d year M.D. student [tape 55], 1981 (Box 47)
          - R., A. M. 2d year M.D. student [tape 56], 1981 (Box 47)
          - Roberts, Chris W. 3d year M.D. [tape 50 (side 2), 57], 1981 (Box 47)
          - S., B. medical school alumnus, 1981 [tape 36], 1982 (Box 47)
          - S., P. medical school alumnus 1981 [tape 36], 1982 (Box 47)
          - Sartorelli, Alan C. chairman, Pharmacology [tapes 58, 59, 60] (Box 47)
          - Spiro, Phillip M. 3d year M.D. student [tape 61], 1981 (Box 47)
          - T., L. A. 4th year M.D. student [tape 6 (side 2), 62], 1981 (Box 47)
          - Thier, Samuel O. chairman, Internal Medicine [tape 63], 1981 (Box 47)
          - Weil, Ulrich, clinical professor, Orthopedics [tape 66], 1981 (Box 47)
          - Weinberg, David H, 4th year M.D. student [tapes 64, 65], 1981 (Box 47)
          - Yeone, Frank E. 4th year M.D. student [tapes 67, 68, 69], 1981 (Box 47)
        - Transcriptions [notes, typescripts]
          - A. G. .K. professor, Psychiatry and Pharmacology, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 193)
          - A. J. E. 4th year M.D. student, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 194)
          - Adimora, Adaoa, 4th year M.D. student, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 195)
          - B. H. R. associate professor, Medicine, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 196)
          - B. R. L. 4th year M.D. student, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 197)
          - B. S. M. 4th year M.D. student, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 198)
          - Baserga, Susan, 3d year M.D./Ph.D student, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 199)
          - Boulpaep, Emile, professor and chairman, Physiology, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 200)
          - Brizendine, Louann, 5th year M.D. student, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 201)